===========================================
Changes 5-4-06
===========================================



6/12/06	Monika: For ARM7 we now pass in phtts into initialize call for Jap, Kor and Chinese so we can get the path to the dictionary file instead of it being hardcoded. chinese .cjk file added to TestTtsDtSimple program
6/7/06	Brian: Modified TextToSpeechSpeakW to make Chinese and Korean find a more fitting text ending location.
5/30/06	Ed: change to slower closer of velum if nasal stop followed by a voiced obstruent.
5/23/06	Ed: first step in chinese "voiced" obstruents
5/22/06	Randall: Changed feature bits of PV, TV, KV, DS, JV, and D1 back to voiced (from voiceless) per Eds request.
5/18/06	Randall: modified durations of KV (pinyin g). Sounds better.
5/18/06	Randall: Fine tuned TV Locus for back vowel F1 and F3
5/18/06	Ed: Found modification from Ken caused problems in transitions from open to voicing glotttis
5/18/06	Randall: Increased duration of X3 (for tone 5 syllable). Also, fine tuned F2 Back locus for TV.
5/18/06	Reiner: syllable duration for long sentences with pauses: "fixed" - here a frame there a frame-chen. Need: better direct synchronization. 
5/18/06	Ed: Tilt fix- It will cause a re-build all
5/18/06	Reiner: sending a break to prevent overflow of synthesizer in long utterances.
5/17/06	Reiner: glottal opening back to 1100 (Ed's initial value) - we are barking up the wrong tree to make a vowel reduction of a segment that's more than one vowel.
5/17/06	Randall: reduced durations of x3 and x2. Made modifications to stops.
5/17/06	Reiner: glottal opening smaller
5/17/06	Randall: Changed Feature bits to voiceless on needed stops and affricates.
5/16/06	Randall: Fine tuned Locus for D1 Rounded. Lengthened UW to 130 for ID and 114 for MDur
5/16/06	Randall: Lengthened duration on OW and remeasured formants.
5/16/06	Randall: Fine tuned locus of D1 front
5/16/06	Ed: remove impulse for now.
5/16/06	Ed: tunign impulse with randall- I reduced it a lot. Plus worked on voiced fricatives the ols nemisis
5/16/06	Randall: Tuned locus of D1 back F1, F2, F3
5/15/06	Ed: closure sometimes had a glitch
5/13/06	Reiner: mandarindurations.c small changes in ending syllable; MandarinF0machine.c modifed tone contours; p_ch_rom.h: modified CH_WO sound 20ms shorter; Ph_drwt02.c: segmental pitch offsets smaller
5/12/06	Leo: added chinese to include path
5/12/06	Randall: changed f1 locus on rounded
5/12/06	Randall: changed duration and formants of WU and locus of TV.
5/12/06	Leo: tts.h now depends on Mandarin.h
5/12/06	Randall: modified duration of WU. Remeasured EY for better sound.
5/12/06	Ed: remove Chinese all encompassing glottal rule
5/11/06	Reiner: changes in F0 contours and further reduction of segmental F0 changes. Modified order of parameters in the subroutine that defines the F0 contours in MandarinF0machine.c
5/11/06	Randall: modified durations and burst of ds to match ts.
5/11/06	Randall: modified affricates: jv,T1, and D1.
5/11/06	Xinchuan: Remove default pinyin from polyphone table and correct some errors for the following: 还,都, 几, 当, 率, 重.
5/11/06	Reiner: F0 segmental effects should not mess up tones: drastically reduced (may be not enough?)
5/11/06	Reiner: removed debugging trick
5/11/06	Reiner: ph_draw.c less of a smoker voice for Chang; ph_drwt02.c f0 segmental targets.
5/11/06	Randall: modifications on the affricates ts, ds, jj, and haven't quite finished jv, t1 and d1 at this point.
5/11/06	Ed: segmentals for reiner's Chinese
5/11/06	Reiner: segmental f0 changes
5/11/06	Ed: misunderstood reiners comment-- revert
5/11/06	Ed: pseudo jitter into Chinese
5/10/06	Reiner: ch_rom.h: higher bandwidth and lower F1 of N and NX. ph_draw.c: further increase of glottal spread for Mandarin S2 and in general.
5/10/06	Reiner: made neutral sounds a bit longer by default as we have now devoicing.
5/10/06	Randall: increased duration of x2 and x3
5/10/06	Ed: revert d1 changes 
5/10/06	Ed: s2 glottal spread for reiner.
5/10/06	Reiner: MAND_S2: means no stress or less stress for neutral tone.
5/10/06	Ed: set bdur for d1 jj and ts for randall
5/09/06	Randall: more tuning on D1 (pinyin zh)
5/09/06	Ed: for Randall fixed the ZHe1
5/09/06	Randall: Mandarin: Worked on D1. Needs more work.
5/08/06	Randall: decreased duration of phonemes x2 and x3 for neutral tone particles. Need to decrease energy of these phonemes. Still to strong for unstressed sounds.
5/05/06	Randall: measured new sound for unstressed particle X2
5/05/06	Randall: Fine tuning on unstressed particle for X3
5/05/06	Reiner: replacement rules for relaxed tone 5 particles
5/05/06	Randall: measured new sound for unstressed Arpa UC (example le5). New arpa sound for this unstressed phoneme is X3.
5/05/06	Randall: fixed EY problem with tone 4. Increased inherent duration to 170 and min dur to 120.
5/05/06	Randall: made changes to AA phoneme. Still not where we want it. Will continue to work on it.
5/05/06	Ed: reduce blade closure speed
5/04/06	Drop to Casio today.
5/04/06	Randall: default of 场 chang3 changed from chang2 to chang3. Verified by Chuck.
5/04/06	Randall: increased min dur of UW to 105 (from 71)
5/04/06	Randall: added comment in CJK.txt regarding a change.
5/03/06	Reiner: UW: ending as back vowel (changed from beginning rounded)
5/03/06	Xinchuan: Add some polyphone entries and correct some errors in previous polyphones.
5/03/06	Xinchuan: More tuning on parameters of variablecubictone() for tone 1-4.
5/03/06	Reiner: changes in 4R: Formant transition. 
changes in CH: second formant deleted (-1) like in German KH.
5/03/06	Xinchuan: Remove some default pinyin entries from polyphone table.Correct some errors in polyphone table. Remove some redundancy in polyphone table.  
5/03/06	Xinchuan: Change default pinyin for 场 from chang2 to chang3.
5/03/06	Ed: voiced fricative changes for all languages and for korean.
5/02/06	Xinchuan: Adjust parameters of calling variablecubictone() for tuning the tones. The related code is controled by MODIFY.
5/02/06	Ed: quick tune of Ya-o-u-e etc (for Japanese), re-tune nasal plus nasal duration, checked in so I can continue work at home...plus remove chine ch kh rule for reiner
5/02/06	Xinchuan: Clean the code related to flag "MODIFY" that is not in use anymore.
5/01/06	Randall: worked on pinyin b (PV arpa).
5/01/06	Randall: Fixed problem with ji4 (JV Arpa). Increased duration. Made palatal. New measurements.
5/01/06	Randall: Fine tuned arpa D1 (pinyin zh). Added more retroflex, retuned formants. Got rid of click. Sounds better.
5/01/06	Randall: tuned arpa UE (umlaut ü in pinyin). Sounds much better. Unmarked plosive in feature bits for arpa DS. This is an unaspirated sound (pinyin z).
5/01/06	Randall: fine tuned arpa diphthong AW. Improved.
4/28/06	Sent Drop to Casio
4/28/06	Reiner: removed print statements
4/28/06	Randall: Reverted this due to a problem: fixed chang2 to go to chang3 (polyphone table change) in this context: 场电
4/28/06	Reiner: yu and lu yuER code changes.
4/28/06	Reiner: bianr change to 1R
4/28/06	Randall: modified min dur of vowels to 50% of Inherent (did not change diphthongs) to make the relative compliance of the vowels higher.
4/27/06	Reiner: overworked F0 control in MandarinF0machine.c: durational dependence of tone patterns for QTA model.
4/27/06	Randall: Increased the duration of final n and ng 25%. (arpa N from 90 to 113) (arpa NX from 120 to 150). Min dur was changed to be 2/3 of the Inherent duration.
4/27/06	Reiner: final lenghthening shortened
4/27/06	Randall: Changed duration of WO from 99 to 142 based on Xinchuans speech
4/27/06	Randall: Measured er-hua uEr (asky G)(arpa 4R). Will be used in place of pinyin finals ui (asky We) and un (asky WXn).
4/27/06	Reiner: C at it's worst (or best in proper hands?): string replacements for er-hua. pinyinparse.c:  mand_replace_rule
4/27/06	Xinchuan: Add Chinese text normalization for time (in the form 12:15:27) and 26 English letters.
4/27/06	Randall: fine tuned er-hua uEr (asky G)(arpa 4R)
4/27/06	Reiner: modifications in er-hua: exceptions and defaults
4/27/06	Reiner: dun -> dWXn in pinying to ascii. thus dunr -> dG .
4/27/06	Randall: in the word dun, changed pinyin to arpa from TVUWAXN to TVWUAXN  (asky u to asky W)
4/27/06	Randall: Measured er-hua allophone üEr (arpa 5R) (asky Y). Sounds good.
4/27/06	Randall: measured yuEr (arpa YR and asky V)
4/26/06	Ed: regarding glottal stop on low vowels - gettar had a misspelling in Chinese prototype and they all should be int's anyway.
4/26/06	Brian: Fixed a bug where the erhua 'r' can't be the first character of a string.
4/26/06	Reiner: changes in tone: timing adjustments with omega_0, plus some fiddling with parameters.
4/26/06	Randall: Mandarin: measured er-hua phoneme iEr (asky F). Now works in er-hua. Also added er-hua testing text to testing file.
4/26/06	Reiner: changes erhua zhi, chi, shi ri zi ci si + er makes a Er, asky B of the vowel.
4/26/06	Chuck: new CJK file from Chuck.  His work in this new file was only on all the 254 'Fonix only' characters. 
4/25/06	Brian: Code was added to handle the "erhua - ugly number 9", as Reiner calls it.  For now all 0x513f characters are converted to pinyin "erhua9" and asky "9".  When Randall has the list of exceptions ready we will implement those.
4/25/06	Reiner: Modified erhua treatment.
4/25/06	Reiner: changed erhua2 to r2
4/25/06	Reiner: fixed erhua on last syll
4/25/06	Brian: Changed the way we handle the erhua case.
4/25/06	Reiner: erhua rule attached 9 at end of syllable triggers modification. works now for both character input or pinyininput
e.g., pinyin input manr1 becomes mar1 
4/24/06	 durations changes update.
4/24/06	 Randall: Finished adding duration parameters for asky J (YI), W (WU),  K (KH), z (DS),  q (JJ),  j (JV),  C (T1),  Z (D1). Still need to add durations and some measurements for some other phonemes. 
4/24/06	Reiner number 9 comment
4/24/06	Randall: Fixed duration and formant measurements of AW (ao). 
4/24/06	Randall: Fixed AY (asky 6). Now sounds good.
4/24/06	Randall: fine tuned EY (ei)
4/24/06	Randall: changed duration on IF to match what was in code.
4/24/06	Randall: added glottal parameters. Getting B-like sound before initial vowel.
4/24/06	Randall: Measured er-hua phoneme UR (asky D). Parameters are now in phedit.
4/21/06	Reiner: (i) Added glottalization signal 'H' if syllable starts with non-high vowel. 
(ii) Modified duration calculations. Note: mindur fields are improperly defined in phedit now. I put in a temporary work-around in mandarindurations.c
(iii) What is the ascky letter for er that triggers er-hua?
4/21/06	Mandarin: added phoneme durations to PHEdit. Haven't finished yet. 
4/21/06	ED: worked on Chinese lve1. He needs to ask Ken about the L.
4/20/06	Randall: Took gan1 options for 干 out of the polyphone table because it is already covered in the CJK text as the default. gan4 is in the polyphone table for 干.
4/20/06	Reiner: reverted half slopes and offset, speedup (about 25 less duration)
fixed one error with large texts, where there was an array overflow. 
4/20/06	Randall: added er-hur rules table.xls for a reference document.
4/20/06	Reiner: durations from phedit table now. Added er hua rules in pinyinparse.c : needs review. Added speaking rate dependent pitch contour (softer for slow speech, harder for fast). In general, for normal rate too slow.
4/19/06	added 2R allophone for er-hua. 
4/19/06	Reiner: Redone: F0 control algorithm -- may need new tuning. Works now "according to theory". Preliminary er-hua rules: remove syllables with er and 
modify previous syllable. Needs testing. 
4/18/06	Ed/Randall: Added er-hua phonemes
4/18/06	Reiner: f0 relative to variable reference
4/18/06	Randall: added "ar" and "or" allophones to p_ch_rom.h
4/18/06	Added Chinese phonemes.
4/18/06	Reiner: modified stretch rules (glides longer and other)
4/18/06	Reiner: initial syllable/final syllable changes
4/18/06	Worked on fine tuning of pinyin c,q,j,s for Chinese
4/13/06	added 休息 to the polyphone table to fix for Casio. The default for 息 is xi1. In the context of 休息 the character  息 becomes xi5. Reference sources: Wenlin and Oxford Chinese dictionary.
4/13/06	Added a few new test phrases to testing archive in subversion.
4/13/06	 Added a test case that caught a bug in the polyphone table lookup.
4/13/06	Ed: remove Debug
4/13/06	Fixed a bug in the polyphone table lookup when repeating characters are used in the same phrase.
4/13/06	Took default 晕 (yun1) out of polyphone table and added the following entries for 晕 (yun4): 晕船,红晕,彩晕,环晕,酒晕,日晕,乳晕,山晕,桃腮微晕,眩晕,血晕,星系晕,眼晕,黑晕,月晕,晕场,晕车,晕池,晕动,晕飞机,晕高儿,晕机,晕轮,晕气,晕色,晕滃图,晕针,子晕. (reference source: Wenlin)
4/13/06	Reiner: MandarinF0machine.c: timing
4/13/06	Ed: remove pribntf
4/13/06	Ed: changes for reiner
4/13/06	Reiner: changes in inital syllable (not ready)
4/12/06	Added 拗 to the polyphone table with ao4 and niu4 as polyphones. ao3 is the default. 
4/12/06	Reiner: cleanup of things in structures no longer needed. Mandarin.h.
4/12/06	Added special case processing for grapheme 0x8C22 (xie4) so that if there are 2 in a row the tone of the second grapheme gets changed.  xie4xie4 -> xie4xie5
4/11/06	Deleted from polyphone table 教 (jiao4) combinations since jiao4 is the default. Added combinations so jiao1 would be generated in context of 教给 (fixed Casio problem with jiao1).
4/11/06	Added 馄饨 to the polyphone table to generate hun2tun5 instead of hun2tun2. 
4/11/06	Xinchuan added Chinese text normalization for currency symbols (including US dollars, Chinese Yuan, UK pound Euro) and for telephone number (format: 123-456-7890).
4/11/06	Reiner added this: timing : initial syllable (call it a cludge ), avoiding overrun for pauses
4/10/06	Fixed Casio problem with dong1xi1 and dong1xi5 variations of 东西. Still more contextual entries need to be added to polyphone table to make more complete. This will be ongoing.
4/10/06	Took out default 的 (pinyin de5) from the polyphone table because it is covered in CJK text. Modified 的 for di4 and di1 in polyphone table.
4/10/06	Added 些东西 to the polyphone table so xie1dong1xi5 pulls up correctly.
4/10/06	Added 后面 to the polyphone table as hou4mian5.  
4/8/06	MandarinF0 : speaking rate and modified control 
4/7/06	Fixed problem with 便宜 so Pian2yi5 is generated instead of bian4yi2
4/7/06	Fixed problem with 的 (de5) being generated as di4 in a certain context. However, I still need to add other contexts to the polyphone table to make it generate correctly in other contexts.
4/7/06	mandarinf0machine: knows about speaker rate, but doesn't know what to do with it. Improved timing, better alignment, more fudge factors removed. Better bugs ;)
4/6/06	Changed durations in code in upcoming model.
4/6/06	Fudge factor removed: omega as characteristic frequency of F0 controller. (MandarinF0machine.c and mandQTAmodel.c) (upcoming tone model)

===========================================
Known bugs 5/4/06
===========================================

1. There is a sudden (unnatural, discontinuing) drop in volume for tone 5 (me5, de5, ma5)
2.can1 sounds like can4, but sounds OK in isolation.
3.guan3 sounds like guan2.
1. Fixed: qu4 is a little too short. Missing some “u’ sound in qu4. 
2. In bai2qu4bao3, there is "t" in "q" for qu4. But qu1,qu2,qu3 are OK.
2. yuan4 is too long.
2. Tone 5 “le5” sounds too strong. In general tone 5 needs to heave lower energy than other tone. Improved.
3. Fixed the pei4 tone problem. zhuang1 is too long. Some noise before “p” in pei4. ei is not sounding right in tone 4.
4. There is noise before “b” in ba3 and bao3, following ng.
5. Shen2 and Mang2 are too long (in general need to work on duration of ng sounds).
6. Fixed: Dao3 sound needs improvement.
7. Improved: ji1ji2yi4yi4 sounds a little too fast.
8. Fixed: zhi1 sounds like zhi4 in zhi1yi4 but sounds OK in zhi1yi2.
9. Duration is too short for some sounds. Working on this.
10. The following sounds need improvement: l, r, ang, vowel in lue (improved lue). Will continue to fine tune the phonemes as needed.
11. Improved: Need to make more natural and fluent 
12. Improved: Tone 5 needs to be shorter.
13. Improved: Need to add more accurate durations to phonemes (new durations have been added to new upcoming tone model). 
14. Improved: r needs more work.
15. Not fixed: Need to add nasal rule reported by Yi. When a nasal (n or ng) is followed by a vowel, the nasal murmur is supposed to be gone but the nasalization remains. (tianamen)
16. Improved, added to text normalization: Not able to pronounce words like ICHIROYAMASHITA  or CA yet. 
17. Working on this: er-hua Er (asky B) needs more er sound.
18. Not completed yet: er-hua exceptions table for 儿 needs to be put in place.
19. Improved: Continue to work on polyphone problems, and need to add more.
20. Fixed: the zh in zhang1 in sentence is not clear (better in isolation).
21. cu sounds like ci in cu4jin4. It sounds ok alone (促进)
Fixed: wei2 should be wei4  为有效地维护
22. Fixed: There is no "u" sound in huir4. 会儿 
23. There is noise before ban1. 的航班 de5hang2ban1.
24. There are some noice before zu1 (fixed zu1) and qi4 (too noisey on q). chu1zu1qi4che1 出租汽车
25. de5da4de5 is jumpy. pai2de5da4de5pi2xiang1. 牌的大的皮箱
26.  Fixed: t shounds like z in tu3. 规划的土建 gui1hua4de5tu3jian4.
27. In tu3 the u is reduced (shouldn't be) . 规划的土建 gui1hua4de5tu3jian4.
28. te4dian3 is too fast 回球落点变化飘忽的特点很快
29. Improved: There is “d” sound in “zh” for Zhong1. 我一个星期上三次中文课。
30. qi4 is too short. 对不起 ,汽车站怎么走？
31. shang4 is too long. 搭地铁上班
32. ju3zhi3 is too fast. 日常的举止就能看出来
33. Fixed: zi4ji3zhi2ye4 is too fast. 拿到了自己职业生涯的第19个冠军
34. There are "t" sounds in qu4 (wo3yao4qu4shu1dian4).
35. Fixed: bei1bei2bei3bei4, (first three bei sounds like bu)
36. In an extra long sentence that is not separated by punctuation, the tone may not be stable.

Below are previous notes from prior version sent to Casio
===========================================
Changes (3 April 2006)
===========================================
Speak application can now read GBK text when Chinese language is selected.
3/14/06	Worked on FO measurements
3/17/06	Changed default of bu4 to bu2 in CJK
3/17/06	Changed default of bu2 back to bu4 in CJK
3/20/06	Added dei3 options to polyphone table.
3/22/06	Reiner added new mandarin FO contour based on consultants methods.
3/24/06	Added document for duration measurements.
3/24/06	Mandarin syllable chart updated.
3/24/06	Mandarin er-hua chart for contractions
3/27/06	Updated er-hua chart
3/27/06	added juan3 to polyphone table. 
3/29/06	Reiner fixed error in previous version, ASKY was wrong
3/30/06	Improved Mandarin r (zr arpa).
3/31/06	Reiner added mandarin durations to upcoming tone model.
3/31/06	 Reiner added new updated version to code (cleaned up). Some code separated.
3/31/06	 Reiner added QTA model.
3/31/06	Sandhi 333 rule by Reiner.
3/31/06	New tone model improved duration, tone, and now tone more stable.
3/31/06	Reiner made modifications on duration, pause duration. Inserting character 9 for reduced er sound for upcoming tone model.  
3/31/06	Updates to mandarin syllable doc.
3/31/06	Duration updates for upcoming tone model.
4/01/06	Reiner added slow phrase F0 contour to upcoming tone model we are working on.
4/3/06	Updated Duration chart of syllables for upcoming mandarin tone model.
4/3/06	Ongoing: We are working to verify Chinese characters. 
4/3/06	Ongoing: making additions to the polyphone table.
4/3/06	We have been working on the tone. Overall tone has improved since last version. On this current model, the tone has smoother transitions between characters. We are currently working on a new tone model that is even more natural and smoother and improved duration of syllables.
4/3/06	Since last drop to Casio have worked on FO measurements from recordings.
4/3/06	Reiner, partially fixed pause problem for upcoming tone model.
4/3/06	Xinchuan working on text normalization.
4/3/06	In March, made improvements to the yi and bu problems. 
4/3/06	Drop to Casio 4/3/06
4/5/06	Yesterday and today, Xinchuan added Chinese text normaliztion for dates, numbers, decimals, percentage, degree for temprature, and degree for angle in math. Fixed the problem that extra text is added when showing Romaji.
4/5/05	Durations from table (measured and literature) times as starting values. There they are scaled somewhat, depending on syllable type, length and tone.  This is for the upcoming tone model.
4/6/06	Fixed problem with shen1. Added to polyphone table.
4/6/06	Tone modification, improved tone. New model to come.
4/6/06	Drop to Casio this AM.


=====================================================
Known bugs 
=====================================================

Fixed:  When testing, please put a space after punctuation (commas, periods, question marks, semi colons etc.).  Otherwise the tone might be off a little.  We are working on fixing this problem.

1. Improved: Need to make more natural and fluent 
2. Fixed: Comma problem with FO
3. Fixed: Alignment problem with tone in upcoming model (at end of sentence sounds bad vs. sounds okay in insolation).
4. Improved: Tone 5 needs to be shorter.
5. Improved: Need to add more accurate durations to phonemes (new durations have been added to new upcoming tone model). 
6. Fixed: can1 sounds like tan1(something has broken)
7. Improved: r needs more work.
8. Fixed: need to add er-hua rules.
9. Fixed: shi4 sounds like shi1.
10. Fixed: "quan" sounds "juan" (something has broken)
11. Fixed: "qian" sounds like "dian" (something has broken)
12. Fixed: Something has been broken.  DT no longer changes characters to Romaji when it is put in the “Show Romaji Translation” mode. 
13. Fixed: 一会儿 is generating yi2hui4er2. Should be yi1huir4
14. Not sure what the ?s are for:  ? comes up as lu:4 in sentence ?????. However, in isolation ? comes up as lv4
15. Fixed: yu3yan2 combines and sounds like one sound. Look into increasing duration of y.
16. Fixed: Shifts in tone in upcoming tone model.
17. Fixed: shu1cai4 sounds like shu4cai2 
18. Not sure what the ?s are for:Transitions among characters in “???” are not smooth in
??????????? in upcoming tone model.
19. Fixed: jian4yi4 sounds like jian1yi1
21. Fixed: ming2 sounds like ming3 in upcoming tone model.
22. Not sure what the ?s are for: ???????? ?? sound is not clear. Need to look into this more. Could be associated with a duration or tone problem.
23. Fixed: Problem with pause.
24. Not fixed: Need to add nasal rule reported by Yi. When a nasal (n or ng) is followed by a vowel, the nasal murmur is supposed to be gone but the nasalization remains. (tianamen)
25. Improved, added to text normalization: Not able to pronounce words like ICHIROYAMASHITA  or CA yet. 
26. Fixed: Problems Reiner is struggling with on the upcoming new tone model.  1.) Can't adjust speaking rate. Synthesizer has internal adjustments that messes up speed.  2.) Can't adjust reference FO 3.) First phoneme gets messed up sometimes, like in the case of pinyin j.
27. Fixed: Crash on Xinchuans model in the following 3 sentences:
      A. 到达时间要晚一些，请保留我的预订。
      B. 晚上好，我叫田中，已经预订了桌子。
      C. 有两次航班，上午和下午的，您想要哪个航班？
28. Fixed: 票 (piao4) the p is not clear in sentence, but is clear in isolation. 
29. Fixed: Difficulty handling long text.
30. Not broken: Stop button not working.
31. Working on this: er-hua Er (asky B) needs more er sound.
32. Not completed yet: er-hua exceptions table for 儿 needs to be put in place.




























